<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Exercises><Exercise><Name>Lawless Lunges</Name><Description>Perform forward lunges while pretending to draw and shoot two imaginary pistols. Embrace your inner cowboy as you feel the burn in your legs.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10</Reps><Rest>30 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>23000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>83000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Open Plains Planks</Name><Description>Get into a plank position and imagine the vast open plains stretching out in front of you. Hold the plank, engaging your core and imagining the freedom of the wild west.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>30 seconds</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>90000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>170000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>River Crossing Squats</Name><Description>Perform squats while imagining crossing a treacherous river. Use your arms to mimic rowing motions, as if helping your wagon safely navigate the water.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>30 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>660000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>750000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Sacrifice Sit-ups</Name><Description>Lie down on your back and perform sit-ups, imagining the difficult choices and sacrifices the pioneers had to make during the river crossing. Feel the burn in your abs as you rise towards a better future.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>700000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>820000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Rhythmical Running in Place</Name><Description>Run in place with a rhythmic bounce, feeling the beat of the music and the connection it brings among the pioneers. Experience the joy of moving together as a community.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>1 minute</Reps><Rest>30 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>1890000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>2010000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Tumbleweed Twists</Name><Description>Stand with your feet hip-width apart and twist your torso from side to side, imagining the dangers and twists of the trail ahead. Engage your core and feel the tension build.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>20</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>2460000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>2560000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Loveless Leg Lifts</Name><Description>Lie on your side and lift your top leg up and down in a controlled motion. Imagine the land not loving you back as you work your outer thighs and glutes.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12 per side</Reps><Rest>30 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>3090000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>3210000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Memories of Mountain Climbers</Name><Description>Get into a high plank position and, one leg at a time, alternate bringing your knees towards your chest. Remember the memories of home as you challenge your core and cardiovascular endurance.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10 per leg</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>3110000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>3230000</TimestampEnd></Exercise></Exercises>
